1
00:09:30,420 --> 00:09:35,420
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

2
00:09:30,420 --> 00:09:35,420
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

3
00:09:30,920 --> 00:09:35,420
{\an5}{\pos(145,227)}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

4
00:09:30,920 --> 00:09:35,420
{\pos(96.4,221.4)}m 50 0 l 179 0 b 208 0 229 21 229 50 l 229 179 b 229 208 208 228 179 228 l 50 228 b 21 228 0 208 0 179 l 0 50 b 0 21 21 0 50 0

5
00:09:30,920 --> 00:09:35,420
{\pos(96.4,221.4)}m 0 0 b 1 -1 2 -2 4 -1 b 7 1 3 2 5 5 b 6 7 8 7 9 5 l 15 -6 b 18 -7 20 -6 20 -3 b 19 -1 17 2 17 4 b 16 7 20 7 21 6 b 22 4 23 2 25 -1 b 27 -2 29 -1 29 1 b 29 2 28 3 29 5 b 30 7 32 7 33 6 b 34 5 34 4 35 3 b 37 2 39 3 39 5 b 39 6 38 8 37 9 b 34 13 29 13 25 9 b 22 13 17 13 13 9 b 10 13 3 13 0 8 

21
00:01:23,380 --> 00:01:24,350
I don't like it.

22
00:01:25,800 --> 00:01:29,010
His businesses are legitimate. Why would he need us?

24
00:01:37,440 --> 00:01:38,980
He's been buying most of the old city

25
00:01:38,980 --> 00:01:42,250
and the outlying areas using holding companies.

26
00:01:42,390 --> 00:01:44,500
The land is mainly worthless,

27
00:01:44,500 --> 00:01:47,770
but I don't understand what he's doing.

29
00:02:23,290 --> 00:02:24,600
Encantado.

30
00:02:25,970 --> 00:02:29,500
Likewise. Have you seen it before?

31
00:02:29,620 --> 00:02:32,940
When I was a kid. Road trip with my parents.

32
00:02:32,940 --> 00:02:35,400
- Hasn't changed a bit. - Hmm.

33
00:02:35,740 --> 00:02:37,280
Let me show you around.

34
00:02:46,950 --> 00:02:48,560
We've upgraded the turbines.

35
00:02:48,560 --> 00:02:51,150
They're rated to last 100 years without maintenance.

36
00:02:51,210 --> 00:02:54,110
All to power... this.

37
00:02:58,550 --> 00:03:00,680
We're looking for resilience.

38
00:03:01,620 --> 00:03:06,910
Our timeline is more ambitious than most.

39
00:03:06,910 --> 00:03:09,410
We offer a unique proposition.

40
00:03:09,410 --> 00:03:13,760
Data has always been fungible. Temporary.

41
00:03:13,770 --> 00:03:17,890
If you invest yours with us, it will be written in stone.

42
00:03:18,290 --> 00:03:20,620
- Forever. - Forever...

43
00:03:21,210 --> 00:03:22,970
...in my experience is a little bit longer

44
00:03:22,970 --> 00:03:24,770
than most people expect.

45
00:03:41,400 --> 00:03:43,870
How much of our platform are you looking to reserve?

46
00:03:43,870 --> 00:03:46,670
- All of it. - Come again?

47
00:03:47,310 --> 00:03:49,970
What I want is already in there.

48
00:03:50,440 --> 00:03:52,140
It was stolen from me.

49
00:03:52,450 --> 00:03:55,750
From one of my facilities, eight years ago.

50
00:03:55,750 --> 00:03:59,000
And I know you were paid handsomely to store it.

51
00:03:59,990 --> 00:04:03,310
I would suggest you take it up with the person who stole it.

52
00:04:03,310 --> 00:04:07,820
I can't. She's dead. Which means I can't decrypt it.

53
00:04:07,820 --> 00:04:09,210
And no one else can.

54
00:04:09,690 --> 00:04:12,560
I don't want it moved or disturbed.

55
00:04:12,620 --> 00:04:14,500
So I'll take the whole shebang.

56
00:04:15,390 --> 00:04:20,340
This is a unique asset, and as such, it's not for sale.

57
00:04:20,830 --> 00:04:24,640
This is America. Everything here is for sale.

58
00:04:27,470 --> 00:04:29,870
That's a pretty good return on your investment.

59
00:04:36,740 --> 00:04:38,370
We know what you've been doing.

60
00:04:38,830 --> 00:04:42,270
You think anyone sells land without our approval?

61
00:04:42,270 --> 00:04:47,380
We've been happy to sell. It's worthless scrubland.

62
00:04:48,740 --> 00:04:50,830
But you can't have this place.

63
00:04:51,540 --> 00:04:53,330
You ever hear the one about the missionary

64
00:04:53,330 --> 00:04:55,680
who tried to negotiate with the tiger?

65
00:04:56,450 --> 00:04:58,240
He told the tiger he could eat most of him,

66
00:04:58,240 --> 00:05:00,900
but he had to stop when he got to his head.

67
00:05:03,440 --> 00:05:04,720
You and your friends in the cartel

68
00:05:04,720 --> 00:05:07,250
or whatever the fuck you're calling yourselves these days

69
00:05:07,250 --> 00:05:09,870
sell me this lump of concrete, today.

70
00:05:11,460 --> 00:05:12,310
Or?

71
00:05:12,700 --> 00:05:15,910
Or you give it to me for nothing. Tomorrow.

72
00:05:17,960 --> 00:05:19,170
We, uh...

73
00:05:20,270 --> 00:05:23,050
we weren't very welcome when we came here.

74
00:05:23,050 --> 00:05:24,090
We had to accept

75
00:05:24,090 --> 00:05:26,750
whatever the old timers offered, at first.

76
00:05:28,270 --> 00:05:31,150
We buried most of them at the bottom of this lake.

77
00:05:32,970 --> 00:05:35,560
Our organization has a long, proud history

78
00:05:35,560 --> 00:05:39,870
of defending itself and its business aggressively.

79
00:05:41,900 --> 00:05:43,720
Door number two, then.

80
00:05:45,260 --> 00:05:46,430
Mañana.

81
00:06:03,810 --> 00:06:04,830
Mañana.

83
00:08:02,590 --> 00:08:06,220
He said that yesterday he would have paid.

84
00:08:07,200 --> 00:08:12,600
But today we would give it to him for nothing.

85
00:09:05,750 --> 00:09:06,690
Thank you.

86
00:09:08,870 --> 00:09:10,210
Is my work done?

87
00:09:11,430 --> 00:09:13,920
Yes. You can rest now.

88
00:12:15,410 --> 00:12:18,420
You're up. I have a dilemma.

89
00:12:20,290 --> 00:12:23,390
Which would you choose? White or black?

90
00:12:25,530 --> 00:12:26,580
Christina?

91
00:12:27,450 --> 00:12:30,580
- They both look great. - Pick a side, Chrissie.

92
00:12:33,940 --> 00:12:35,600
What are you wearing tonight?

93
00:12:36,080 --> 00:12:38,290
Uh, this?

94
00:12:39,780 --> 00:12:40,580
Right.

95
00:12:42,240 --> 00:12:43,540
It looks great,

96
00:12:43,540 --> 00:12:46,740
unlike these damn bags under my eyes.

97
00:12:46,740 --> 00:12:48,440
I look like a zombie.

98
00:12:48,960 --> 00:12:51,540
- Bad night's sleep? - Nightmares.

99
00:12:51,880 --> 00:12:53,450
Maybe I should've taken a tab.

100
00:12:53,450 --> 00:12:56,440
But, uh, I just kept tossing and turning.

103
00:13:04,770 --> 00:13:06,330
Is it that weirdo again?

104
00:13:06,340 --> 00:13:08,280
I blocked him, but he keeps getting through.

105
00:13:08,280 --> 00:13:09,450
It's just some creep

106
00:13:09,450 --> 00:13:12,480
or a bot trying to sell you a privacy subscription.

107
00:13:12,550 --> 00:13:13,550
I guess.

108
00:13:15,990 --> 00:13:18,410
Lately, I feel like someone's watching me.

109
00:13:18,410 --> 00:13:20,330
No offense, but how?

110
00:13:20,610 --> 00:13:22,900
I mean, except for work, you don't leave the apartment,

111
00:13:22,900 --> 00:13:25,890
which is why you're coming out tonight.

112
00:13:26,500 --> 00:13:28,650
I mean, he's supposed to be a really nice guy.

113
00:13:28,650 --> 00:13:30,760
And his profile's platinum rated.

114
00:13:31,500 --> 00:13:34,220
Set-ups are just so awkward.

115
00:13:36,210 --> 00:13:37,910
And so is dying alone.

116
00:13:37,910 --> 00:13:41,340
You cannot hide from the world forever, Christina.

117
00:13:44,190 --> 00:13:45,020
Okay.

118
00:14:17,380 --> 00:14:18,490
That was insane.

119
00:14:18,490 --> 00:14:20,050
This is way better than I expected.

120
00:14:20,050 --> 00:14:22,160
This place is fucking wild.

121
00:14:22,160 --> 00:14:24,720
Can't believe this is your first time.

122
00:14:24,790 --> 00:14:25,440
Come on.

123
00:14:25,440 --> 00:14:27,570
I know a spot that's really gonna blow your mind.

124
00:14:36,790 --> 00:14:37,830
Can you see it?

125
00:14:37,910 --> 00:14:41,700
It's looming over us. The tower! Can you see it? Huh?

126
00:14:42,160 --> 00:14:45,070
Can you see it? Can you see it?

128
00:15:27,690 --> 00:15:28,920
Record pitch.

129
00:15:31,220 --> 00:15:32,520
There's a young girl.

130
00:15:34,160 --> 00:15:35,370
Not that young.

131
00:15:36,220 --> 00:15:38,630
More like late teens.

132
00:15:40,030 --> 00:15:44,200
She lives at home with her father in the country.

133
00:15:46,790 --> 00:15:49,010
Scratch that. The city.

134
00:15:51,390 --> 00:15:52,360
He's a little infirm,

135
00:15:52,360 --> 00:15:54,550
so she spends most of her time with him.

136
00:15:55,010 --> 00:15:56,930
But she dreams of a bigger life

137
00:15:57,440 --> 00:16:02,390
with excitement, adventure, romance.

138
00:16:03,260 --> 00:16:04,180
Christina.

139
00:16:05,940 --> 00:16:07,160
Pause record.

140
00:16:09,800 --> 00:16:12,120
We need to talk about your work performance.

141
00:16:12,490 --> 00:16:14,720
I mean, don't you want to advance in your career?

142
00:16:15,350 --> 00:16:17,420
- Of course I do. - Well, then you got to stop

143
00:16:17,420 --> 00:16:20,020
pitching these saccharine stories.

144
00:16:20,020 --> 00:16:23,420
You know, people want sex, danger, violence,

145
00:16:23,420 --> 00:16:26,950
transgressions, melodrama. They want tragedy.

146
00:16:26,980 --> 00:16:29,710
- Yada, yada, yada. - I know.

147
00:16:31,420 --> 00:16:33,580
I-- I was thinking maybe I could write

148
00:16:33,580 --> 00:16:36,420
in some different genres to broaden it out.

149
00:16:36,420 --> 00:16:40,060
Maybe a little romance, some humor.

150
00:16:40,060 --> 00:16:42,190
Maybe just save that for your diary.

151
00:16:43,340 --> 00:16:44,240
I know you've got it in you

152
00:16:44,240 --> 00:16:45,920
to write the kind of copy we need.

153
00:16:46,190 --> 00:16:48,560
Now, take that story you wrote a couple months back.

154
00:16:48,830 --> 00:16:51,510
Poor schmuck loses everything, drowns his sorrows,

155
00:16:51,510 --> 00:16:54,630
stalks some girl. How'd it end again?

156
00:16:56,120 --> 00:16:58,990
- Everyone dies. - Yes. That's right.

157
00:16:59,140 --> 00:17:00,370
It's a real tearjerker.

158
00:17:01,980 --> 00:17:04,840
Just, uh, bring more of that.

159
00:17:06,130 --> 00:17:08,760
Or else I'm gonna have to find another writer who can.

160
00:17:09,520 --> 00:17:12,420
- Understood? - Yes. Of course.

161
00:17:12,500 --> 00:17:13,400
All right.

163
00:17:34,860 --> 00:17:36,770
Hello? You hear me?

164
00:17:37,090 --> 00:17:40,120
I know you're out there. I saw what you wrote.

165
00:17:40,390 --> 00:17:42,170
Why are you doing this to us?

166
00:17:42,170 --> 00:17:45,580
You have to help me. Your game is ruining my life--

167
00:18:12,530 --> 00:18:15,150
Always a classic by the inimitable Hendrix.

168
00:18:15,160 --> 00:18:18,660
And now, back to our coverage of the festivities.

169
00:18:18,660 --> 00:18:21,260
Preparations are underway for this year's...

170
00:19:04,610 --> 00:19:05,880
Are you ready, darling?

171
00:19:05,880 --> 00:19:08,540
- For what? - This is the new world.

172
00:19:08,540 --> 00:19:13,300
And in this world, you can be whoever the fuck you want.

173
00:19:56,650 --> 00:19:58,210
Oh, for fuck's sake...

174
00:20:39,050 --> 00:20:40,850
Got any plans for the anniversary?

175
00:20:44,020 --> 00:20:46,580
Nah. Just work.

176
00:20:47,430 --> 00:20:49,530
Cashing in on that overtime, eh?

177
00:20:49,930 --> 00:20:50,950
Man, seven years ago,

178
00:20:50,950 --> 00:20:53,720
it would've just been robots working the holiday, but...

179
00:20:54,160 --> 00:20:56,580
lucky for us, they're all scrap metal now.

180
00:20:57,480 --> 00:20:59,840
Least the riots ensured our job security.

181
00:20:59,910 --> 00:21:03,140
That wasn't exactly the point of the riots.

182
00:21:03,140 --> 00:21:05,440
Yeah, 'cause the riots had no point.

183
00:21:05,870 --> 00:21:07,340
They won us our freedom.

184
00:21:07,480 --> 00:21:10,480
Sure, but from what? Ourselves?

185
00:21:10,910 --> 00:21:12,300
Hey, man, the way I look at it,

186
00:21:12,300 --> 00:21:13,900
that Incite machine that they blew up

187
00:21:13,900 --> 00:21:17,410
didn't tell us who we could be, it told us who we already were.

188
00:21:17,910 --> 00:21:22,120
- You actually believe that? - Don't you? Let me ask you this.

189
00:21:23,020 --> 00:21:25,660
Has your life changed since they destroyed those machines?

190
00:22:18,220 --> 00:22:21,200
You haven't been practicing enough.

191
00:22:21,200 --> 00:22:22,210
Dad!

192
00:22:25,350 --> 00:22:26,900
Good to see you, Cookie.

193
00:22:27,120 --> 00:22:29,330
Here. All right.

194
00:22:38,600 --> 00:22:43,170
- How'd you do that? - Like I said, practice.

195
00:22:43,360 --> 00:22:44,420
A lot of it.

196
00:22:45,570 --> 00:22:47,120
On cans?

197
00:22:48,410 --> 00:22:50,510
Yeah. On cans.

198
00:22:50,800 --> 00:22:51,640
Here.

199
00:23:01,190 --> 00:23:02,110
O'kay.

200
00:23:04,050 --> 00:23:05,930
Remember. This.

201
00:23:07,310 --> 00:23:08,610
Now stare at it.

202
00:23:09,710 --> 00:23:11,090
Okay. Visualize.

203
00:23:12,440 --> 00:23:13,460
Breathe out.

204
00:23:14,900 --> 00:23:15,960
Hold steady.

205
00:23:17,190 --> 00:23:18,940
And squeeze.

206
00:23:18,950 --> 00:23:21,000
Frankie! Caleb!

207
00:23:24,970 --> 00:23:26,630
I was visualizing.

208
00:23:26,630 --> 00:23:29,280
Well, come inside and visualize meatloaf.

210
00:23:30,900 --> 00:23:34,510
Just a little longer? - C'mon, listen to your mother.

211
00:23:38,490 --> 00:23:39,350
Coming.

212
00:23:44,920 --> 00:23:45,830
Go wash up.

213
00:23:47,920 --> 00:23:49,730
Enough with the cowboy shit.

214
00:23:50,340 --> 00:23:52,500
- She likes it. - She's seven, Caleb.

215
00:23:52,500 --> 00:23:55,830
Thanks to you, her hobbies are sugar and violence.

216
00:24:04,490 --> 00:24:06,620
Look, I'm sorry.

217
00:24:07,580 --> 00:24:09,450
I know it's not an easy day for you,

218
00:24:09,450 --> 00:24:12,680
but the war is over.

219
00:24:13,500 --> 00:24:15,480
It's time you start living that way.

220
00:24:16,990 --> 00:24:17,790
Okay?

221
00:24:20,080 --> 00:24:21,460
Go set the table.

222
00:24:22,280 --> 00:24:24,050
What's the magic word?

223
00:24:26,230 --> 00:24:27,370
Divorce.

224
00:24:32,910 --> 00:24:34,530
Love you too.

225
00:25:07,620 --> 00:25:09,680
You lose power the other night?

226
00:25:10,580 --> 00:25:12,090
Must've been spared.

227
00:25:12,840 --> 00:25:16,230
You, uh, sure you don't want some extra bottles for your guests?

228
00:25:16,930 --> 00:25:17,870
Guests?

229
00:25:18,250 --> 00:25:19,250
Your friends.

230
00:25:19,620 --> 00:25:21,150
Stopped by asking for directions.

231
00:25:21,150 --> 00:25:22,850
I tried to describe it,

232
00:25:22,850 --> 00:25:26,350
but you live pretty far off the beaten path.

233
00:25:26,350 --> 00:25:29,000
You really should get a sat phone or,

234
00:25:29,000 --> 00:25:31,230
- some kind of connec-- - These friends of mine,

235
00:25:31,490 --> 00:25:33,300
how long ago did they stop by?

236
00:25:33,670 --> 00:25:35,640
Not 20 minutes since you been in.

237
00:25:40,760 --> 00:25:42,180
On second thought,

238
00:25:42,450 --> 00:25:45,130
why don't you go ahead and add that to my tab?

239
00:26:37,330 --> 00:26:38,220
Fire!

240
00:27:57,790 --> 00:27:59,110
How did you find me?

241
00:27:59,340 --> 00:28:02,360
Two days ago. We got a signal.

242
00:28:02,870 --> 00:28:06,530
Your little power outage. It was enough.

243
00:28:07,400 --> 00:28:08,980
How many more are after me?

244
00:28:09,110 --> 00:28:12,300
I'm no-- not at liberty to say.

245
00:28:12,300 --> 00:28:13,710
Well, let me liberate you.

246
00:28:13,910 --> 00:28:16,010
Seven years, I've been off the grid alone,

247
00:28:16,860 --> 00:28:18,090
not bothering anyone.

248
00:28:18,650 --> 00:28:21,150
And yet here you are darkening my door.

249
00:28:23,130 --> 00:28:24,690
Who sent you, Colonel Brigham?

250
00:28:24,980 --> 00:28:26,420
Who the fuck is that?

251
00:28:26,720 --> 00:28:29,420
I'm afraid I don't have the patience to explain.

252
00:28:30,830 --> 00:28:32,000
Now be a dear.

253
00:28:33,000 --> 00:28:34,290
Close your eyes, won't you?

254
00:29:05,000 --> 00:29:06,150
Go get her.

255
00:29:08,020 --> 00:29:09,820
I've got no idea she's home or not.

256
00:29:09,820 --> 00:29:11,150
Haven't seen her in a couple days.

257
00:29:23,310 --> 00:29:24,340
Shit.

258
00:30:41,780 --> 00:30:42,980
Welcome home.

259
00:30:57,470 --> 00:31:00,070
- Hello? - You on your way?

260
00:31:01,340 --> 00:31:02,820
Shit. I forgot.

261
00:31:02,840 --> 00:31:04,210
You didn't forget.

262
00:31:04,550 --> 00:31:05,910
You repressed.

263
00:31:06,360 --> 00:31:08,500
I'm not going to be an accessory after the fact

264
00:31:08,500 --> 00:31:11,190
to the murder of your social life. Let's go.

265
00:31:11,190 --> 00:31:12,190
But--

266
00:32:18,510 --> 00:32:20,520
Look, I'm sure it was nothing.

267
00:32:20,590 --> 00:32:22,420
Probably that kid from the fourth floor

268
00:32:22,430 --> 00:32:24,420
that likes to smoke weed on the fire escape.

269
00:32:24,420 --> 00:32:26,740
- Yeah. Right. - You want some?

270
00:32:26,910 --> 00:32:27,960
No, I'm okay.

271
00:32:29,920 --> 00:32:31,680
Here. In case.

272
00:32:32,600 --> 00:32:36,070
And remember, smile. You have to at least try.

273
00:32:36,850 --> 00:32:37,820
Do I?

274
00:32:38,310 --> 00:32:41,180
I mean, even if by some miracle we're right for each other,

275
00:32:41,180 --> 00:32:44,060
shouldn't it be natural and easy?

276
00:32:44,130 --> 00:32:45,280
Are you kidding?

277
00:32:45,940 --> 00:32:50,410
Take a look at this world. Nobody wants easy or natural.

278
00:32:51,000 --> 00:32:53,780
Art is a lie that tells the truth, honey.

279
00:32:54,800 --> 00:32:57,520
And the truth is, you need to get laid.

280
00:33:03,280 --> 00:33:07,390
Look at this. All the people. You like people.

281
00:33:07,390 --> 00:33:10,550
- You should try breathing. - I should get a drink.

282
00:33:10,570 --> 00:33:12,200
Yes, you should. It's going to be great.

283
00:33:13,940 --> 00:33:15,140
Thank you.

284
00:33:16,960 --> 00:33:18,990
Just give me the signal if he's a dud.

285
00:33:23,320 --> 00:33:25,160
And don't forget to smile.

286
00:33:30,310 --> 00:33:31,660
Most people think it's just elite gambling,

287
00:33:31,660 --> 00:33:34,070
but there's a system to investing.

288
00:33:34,070 --> 00:33:36,740
Patterns that some minds can decipher.

289
00:33:37,310 --> 00:33:38,510
If there weren't, I wouldn't be sitting

290
00:33:38,510 --> 00:33:40,680
in this lovely restaurant drinking superb wine

291
00:33:40,680 --> 00:33:42,090
with such fine company.

292
00:33:45,120 --> 00:33:48,430
So, enough about me. What is it you do, again?

293
00:33:49,390 --> 00:33:51,980
I'm a writer for Olympiad Entertainment.

294
00:33:53,200 --> 00:33:54,120
Thank you.

295
00:33:55,340 --> 00:33:56,910
Wh-- what games do you write for?

296
00:33:57,170 --> 00:33:58,270
Maybe I've played them.

297
00:33:59,540 --> 00:34:01,240
I've been working on a new game.

298
00:34:01,970 --> 00:34:04,090
It doesn't have a name yet. It's still in beta.

299
00:34:04,250 --> 00:34:06,070
But even after it's released,

300
00:34:06,070 --> 00:34:07,050
you probably won't know my work.

301
00:34:07,050 --> 00:34:09,500
I mostly write non player characters.

302
00:34:09,640 --> 00:34:10,620
What's that?

303
00:34:11,090 --> 00:34:13,010
Background characters that interact with the players

304
00:34:13,010 --> 00:34:14,250
on their journeys.

305
00:34:14,650 --> 00:34:16,840
Not as high-profile as programming the leads.

306
00:34:16,850 --> 00:34:18,370
But it's just as important.

307
00:34:18,370 --> 00:34:20,100
For most players, the background characters

308
00:34:20,100 --> 00:34:21,780
are just cannon fodder.

309
00:34:25,260 --> 00:34:26,640
I'm not doing it for the players,

310
00:34:26,640 --> 00:34:27,920
I'm doing it for myself.

311
00:34:29,430 --> 00:34:30,540
How so?

312
00:34:32,820 --> 00:34:35,810
Real life can be disappointing.

313
00:34:37,220 --> 00:34:41,180
Not that it's so bad. Just... there should be more to it.

314
00:34:44,390 --> 00:34:46,490
Maybe you just haven't found the right man yet.

315
00:34:53,200 --> 00:34:54,530
You sound depressed.

316
00:34:56,520 --> 00:34:57,880
There's tabs for that.

317
00:34:59,600 --> 00:35:00,870
They'll fix you right up.

318
00:35:02,810 --> 00:35:04,170
What if I'm not the one that's broken?

319
00:35:04,170 --> 00:35:06,080
What if it's the world that needs fixing?

320
00:35:07,090 --> 00:35:08,760
There's tabs for that feeling, too.

321
00:35:10,910 --> 00:35:11,880
Of course.

322
00:35:15,550 --> 00:35:16,750
Will you excuse me?

323
00:36:06,490 --> 00:36:08,080
- Please stop calling me. - Wait, wait!

324
00:36:08,080 --> 00:36:10,720
Don't hang up. You need to help me.

325
00:36:11,150 --> 00:36:12,200
The doctors think I'm crazy.

326
00:36:12,210 --> 00:36:15,360
But I know you're real. Just like the tower is real.

327
00:36:15,830 --> 00:36:18,160
You need to stop what you're doing.

328
00:36:18,160 --> 00:36:19,580
I told you, I'm not doing anything.

329
00:36:19,580 --> 00:36:21,340
You're destroying my life.

330
00:36:21,360 --> 00:36:23,220
I'm not. I don't even know you.

331
00:36:23,380 --> 00:36:24,690
You can't hide from me.

332
00:36:25,340 --> 00:36:26,790
I will find you.

333
00:36:26,790 --> 00:36:30,440
Do you understand? You have to end this, or I will.

334
00:36:30,440 --> 00:36:32,260
You need help, and I hope you get it.

335
00:36:32,260 --> 00:36:33,790
But next time you call, I'm going to the police.

336
00:36:33,790 --> 00:36:35,110
No, no, don't hang-- -

337
00:36:42,740 --> 00:36:43,790
Yeah, I'm surprised.

338
00:36:43,790 --> 00:36:45,180
I just bumped into a work friend.

339
00:36:45,180 --> 00:36:46,150
Oh, really?

340
00:36:46,150 --> 00:36:48,130
I think I'm gonna be out for a while.

341
00:36:48,130 --> 00:36:49,680
Don't be discouraged about tonight.

342
00:36:49,690 --> 00:36:50,920
Are you sure you're okay?

343
00:36:51,070 --> 00:36:54,100
Maya, it's fine, really. Have fun.

344
00:36:54,230 --> 00:36:56,270
- Where are you? - I'm almost home.

345
00:36:56,270 --> 00:36:59,160
Okay, good. I gotta go. You're okay?

346
00:36:59,160 --> 00:37:00,050
- Yeah. - Take care.

347
00:37:00,050 --> 00:37:00,940
Bye.

348
00:37:08,840 --> 00:37:10,090
- Sorry about that. - It's my fault.

349
00:37:10,090 --> 00:37:11,750
I wasn't paying attention.

350
00:37:16,470 --> 00:37:18,880
I, uh, I didn't see you there.

351
00:37:19,950 --> 00:37:22,620
- But now I do. - It's okay.

352
00:37:23,690 --> 00:37:24,720
You scared me.

353
00:37:26,330 --> 00:37:29,270
- I guess we're even. - I'm Peter.

354
00:37:30,030 --> 00:37:32,390
I-- I just have to get home. My roommate's waiting for me.

355
00:37:32,390 --> 00:37:34,720
I've been wanting to meet you for such a long time.

356
00:37:35,070 --> 00:37:37,320
- Excuse me? - I knew you existed.

357
00:37:37,600 --> 00:37:40,630
I was worried you weren't real, but here you are.

358
00:37:41,530 --> 00:37:43,180
Why are you doing this to us?

359
00:37:48,370 --> 00:37:50,440
It's you. You're the one who's been calling.

360
00:37:50,440 --> 00:37:51,980
I need to ask you to leave us alone.

361
00:37:51,980 --> 00:37:53,600
- No. - No, stop!

362
00:37:53,630 --> 00:37:54,800
Stop! No, no, no!

363
00:37:54,800 --> 00:37:56,130
- No! - This isn't who I am.

364
00:37:56,130 --> 00:37:58,710
- Get away from me! - Please, this is important.

365
00:37:59,110 --> 00:38:01,360
I lost my job, my wife.

366
00:38:01,880 --> 00:38:03,770
I thought it was the tower. But...

367
00:38:06,650 --> 00:38:09,960
it was you. You made me do those things.

368
00:38:09,970 --> 00:38:11,970
All these people do what you want them to.

369
00:38:11,970 --> 00:38:12,650
I don't know what you're talking about--

370
00:38:12,650 --> 00:38:14,770
- No! - No, no, let me go!

371
00:38:14,860 --> 00:38:15,820
You need to stop!

372
00:38:15,820 --> 00:38:17,000
No! No! No!

373
00:38:18,810 --> 00:38:20,450
How did you know so much about us?

374
00:38:21,320 --> 00:38:21,710
The game.

375
00:38:21,710 --> 00:38:22,820
You wrote us into it. How?

376
00:38:22,820 --> 00:38:25,260
Listen to me. Listen to me. Pe-- Peter--

377
00:38:27,430 --> 00:38:29,510
I'm so sorry for everything that's happened to you.

378
00:38:29,880 --> 00:38:32,190
But I have nothing do with that. I can't help you.

379
00:38:32,710 --> 00:38:33,920
You need to help me.

380
00:38:35,800 --> 00:38:37,470
I need for the story to change.

381
00:38:37,470 --> 00:38:39,150
I need the ending to be different.

382
00:38:42,450 --> 00:38:43,880
- I'm sorry. - No!

383
00:38:51,130 --> 00:38:52,310
Get off me, man!

384
00:39:13,550 --> 00:39:15,420
"They heard a voice scream,

385
00:39:15,470 --> 00:39:18,490
'We need our dragon!'

386
00:39:18,830 --> 00:39:21,590
But my father and the dragon knew

387
00:39:21,590 --> 00:39:24,680
that nothing in the world would ever make them go back

388
00:39:25,120 --> 00:39:29,470
to Wild Island. The end."

389
00:39:30,090 --> 00:39:32,440
All right. Time to tuck in.

390
00:39:41,550 --> 00:39:42,530
All right.

391
00:39:42,830 --> 00:39:45,100
You and Bear Bear sleep good, all right?

392
00:39:47,100 --> 00:39:48,890
Can we leave the lights on tonight?

393
00:39:50,350 --> 00:39:53,140
- Why would we do that? - Bear Bear's scared.

394
00:39:53,200 --> 00:39:55,330
I told him I'd keep watch over him.

395
00:39:56,870 --> 00:39:59,620
Well, you know the best way to keep watch at night

396
00:40:00,050 --> 00:40:02,260
is to turn the lights down around you and light up--

397
00:40:02,260 --> 00:40:03,940
Light up the perimeter.

398
00:40:04,740 --> 00:40:07,640
That way, no one can see you, but you can see.

399
00:40:09,680 --> 00:40:10,730
See everyone.

400
00:40:11,490 --> 00:40:14,760
Look, um, Bear Bear doesn't need to think about this stuff.

401
00:40:14,770 --> 00:40:18,160
Okay? Everyone is safe and sound.

402
00:40:18,760 --> 00:40:19,850
Promise?

403
00:40:22,470 --> 00:40:23,710
I promise.

404
00:40:25,070 --> 00:40:26,100
Okay, goodnight.

405
00:40:35,550 --> 00:40:38,960
- Did you hear that? - It's probably nothing.

406
00:40:48,550 --> 00:40:49,750
Goodnight, Mom.

407
00:40:50,270 --> 00:40:52,370
Come on, let's get you in bed.

408
00:41:02,740 --> 00:41:03,740
Fuck!

409
00:41:06,760 --> 00:41:08,500
What the hell is this, Caleb?

410
00:41:08,860 --> 00:41:10,310
There is something out there.

411
00:41:10,310 --> 00:41:14,440
Yeah. A raccoon or a neighbor or a delivery man.

412
00:41:15,850 --> 00:41:17,280
We've been through this.

413
00:41:18,230 --> 00:41:22,800
You just need to take deep breaths. Calm yourself.

414
00:41:23,450 --> 00:41:25,150
The past is in the past.

415
00:41:25,380 --> 00:41:28,330
Nothing is going to hurt you except your own mind.

416
00:41:29,620 --> 00:41:30,570
I'm sorry.

417
00:42:23,040 --> 00:42:24,600
Are you gonna help me or not?

418
00:42:28,970 --> 00:42:30,520
Peter, I know that you're upset,

419
00:42:31,340 --> 00:42:32,770
but whatever you think is happening,

420
00:42:33,400 --> 00:42:34,770
you're just confused.

421
00:42:36,740 --> 00:42:38,160
So you're not gonna help.

422
00:42:39,080 --> 00:42:40,750
I wish I could, but the stories that I write,

423
00:42:40,750 --> 00:42:41,790
they're not real.

424
00:42:43,360 --> 00:42:44,970
Do you remember how mine ends?

425
00:42:47,790 --> 00:42:48,790
What?

426
00:42:52,700 --> 00:42:55,020
- Peter, where are you? - Look up.

427
00:43:05,200 --> 00:43:08,480
Is this up to me, or did you write this, too?

428
00:43:44,450 --> 00:43:46,140
I found it under her pillow.

429
00:43:47,460 --> 00:43:49,460
You're rubbing off on her, Caleb.

430
00:43:50,250 --> 00:43:50,990
Isn't that a good thing?

431
00:43:50,990 --> 00:43:53,650
Not when she's pretending to have PTSD.

432
00:43:54,270 --> 00:43:55,170
I see the messages

433
00:43:55,170 --> 00:43:57,300
you and your war buddies send to each other.

434
00:43:57,300 --> 00:43:59,580
Chemtrails, government cover-ups.

435
00:43:59,580 --> 00:44:01,620
You see threats everywhere,

436
00:44:01,620 --> 00:44:02,950
and now so does Frankie.

437
00:44:03,230 --> 00:44:06,200
Look, I am not paranoid.

438
00:44:12,890 --> 00:44:14,230
Maybe you're right.

439
00:44:15,310 --> 00:44:18,660
I'm beginning to think it's not that you fear war,

440
00:44:19,680 --> 00:44:21,930
- it's that you miss it. - Oh, my...

441
00:44:21,930 --> 00:44:24,090
This life is too ordinary for you.

442
00:44:25,710 --> 00:44:26,700
What?

443
00:44:28,220 --> 00:44:31,260
You have a job, a home,

444
00:44:32,610 --> 00:44:38,430
a beautiful child, and a very patient wife.

445
00:44:39,890 --> 00:44:41,630
But it's never enough, is it?

446
00:45:05,980 --> 00:45:07,370
False alarm, Bear Bear.

447
00:45:09,430 --> 00:45:11,570
See? It's just a raccoon.

448
00:45:13,030 --> 00:45:14,150
Crap.

449
00:45:53,510 --> 00:45:54,560
Hey there.

450
00:45:58,330 --> 00:45:59,640
Is your daddy home?

451
00:46:03,260 --> 00:46:05,670
Daddy, this man wants to talk to you.

452
00:46:05,670 --> 00:46:06,610
Frankie!

453
00:46:26,490 --> 00:46:28,110
I believe this is yours.

454
00:46:35,820 --> 00:46:38,830
- Who are you? - An old friend.

455
00:46:40,020 --> 00:46:41,300
Caleb!

456
00:46:43,380 --> 00:46:46,510
Frankie! Are you okay?

457
00:46:46,510 --> 00:46:48,610
- Go inside. - Okay. Are you okay?

458
00:47:00,140 --> 00:47:01,610
Hello, darling.

459
00:47:03,010 --> 00:47:04,330
It's really you.

460
00:47:05,710 --> 00:47:06,900
You know, I thought...

461
00:47:07,930 --> 00:47:10,450
I was sure I was never gonna see you again.

462
00:47:11,220 --> 00:47:12,780
And yet here I am,

463
00:47:13,410 --> 00:47:17,060
disposing and dismembering just like the good old days.

464
00:47:18,640 --> 00:47:20,580
If something happened to my daughter,

465
00:47:20,580 --> 00:47:21,780
you have no idea--

466
00:47:21,780 --> 00:47:23,290
I have every idea...

467
00:47:25,100 --> 00:47:27,270
which is why it won't come to that.

468
00:47:28,790 --> 00:47:30,980
I know who sent those men after us.

469
00:47:32,680 --> 00:47:33,700
William.

470
00:47:34,520 --> 00:47:35,750
He's back at it.

471
00:47:56,660 --> 00:48:00,430
I, uh... Frankie's asleep. Thank God.

472
00:48:01,500 --> 00:48:04,500
I called Carver. The guys are downstairs.

473
00:48:05,700 --> 00:48:08,070
All these years, I thought you were paranoid.

474
00:48:12,720 --> 00:48:14,560
But the war isn't over, is it?

475
00:48:18,700 --> 00:48:22,200
No, it is me they wanted.

476
00:48:23,790 --> 00:48:25,670
Look, I am the one who brought this upon us.

477
00:48:25,670 --> 00:48:28,750
And I am the one who has to end it.

478
00:48:30,890 --> 00:48:32,090
So you're leaving.

479
00:48:34,860 --> 00:48:36,590
Only for a little while.

480
00:48:38,910 --> 00:48:41,510
You promised you'd be a father.

481
00:48:42,120 --> 00:48:46,280
I am one. Everything I do is for you...

482
00:48:48,190 --> 00:48:49,690
and for Frankie.

483
00:48:52,770 --> 00:48:54,640
You're going to get yourself killed.

484
00:48:56,220 --> 00:48:58,100
Hey, I will come back to you.

485
00:48:59,540 --> 00:49:00,730
I promise.

486
00:50:01,450 --> 00:50:02,470
All right.

487
00:50:03,480 --> 00:50:05,060
- You know the drill. - You got it.

488
00:50:08,240 --> 00:50:10,120
I always knew this day was coming.

489
00:50:10,530 --> 00:50:11,970
As soon as you stop running,

490
00:50:11,970 --> 00:50:13,820
everyone else starts to catch up.

491
00:50:14,840 --> 00:50:17,440
- Any idea why now? - I don't know.

492
00:50:17,950 --> 00:50:19,970
But I had a little tête-à-tête

493
00:50:19,980 --> 00:50:21,960
with the one that they sent after me.

494
00:50:22,510 --> 00:50:24,610
We're not the only ones William was after.

495
00:50:25,220 --> 00:50:28,330
He was very interested in talking to a Senator in California.

496
00:50:28,400 --> 00:50:30,120
Then we should get to him first.

497
00:50:32,590 --> 00:50:33,630
We?

498
00:50:35,200 --> 00:50:36,350
I'm coming.

499
00:50:37,130 --> 00:50:38,800
It's the only way I can protect my family.

500
00:50:38,800 --> 00:50:41,870
I'll be fine on my own. You can stay here.

501
00:50:42,420 --> 00:50:44,520
- You probably should. - Would you?

502
00:50:46,350 --> 00:50:47,400
No.

503
00:50:50,460 --> 00:50:51,810
But I'd regret it.

504
00:51:20,010 --> 00:51:21,360
Record pitch.

505
00:51:23,870 --> 00:51:25,410
I want to write a new story.

506
00:51:28,610 --> 00:51:32,780
About a girl... A girl who's searching.

507
00:51:36,660 --> 00:51:38,910
The girl doesn't know what she's searching for.

508
00:51:46,640 --> 00:51:51,380
She just knows there is an emptiness in her life.

509
00:51:58,120 --> 00:51:59,850
Or maybe it's inside her.

510
00:52:04,810 --> 00:52:08,470
And when she finds the thing she's searching for,

511
00:52:08,770 --> 00:52:10,490
everything will make sense.

512
00:52:16,360 --> 00:52:18,440
I want a story with a happy ending.

513
00:52:32,470 --> 00:52:33,520
Stupid.

514
00:52:35,470 --> 00:52:37,840
Stupid stories nobody wants to hear.

